[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":49564,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":76998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":21285,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":98285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":22911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":121200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1693,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":122898,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5460,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":128360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1331,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":129695,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result.) ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5697,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":135402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1389,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":136793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4250,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":141045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2  because  1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1723,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":142770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3735,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":146507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":6742,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":153251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the  first nu mber, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5186,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":158439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1601,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":160043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3748,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":163793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1884,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":165679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3709,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":169390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1167,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":170559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3433,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":173994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":7379,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":181376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you  subtrac t 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":186946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1395,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":188346,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":19568,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":207918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":70769,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":278690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":285915,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1816,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":287733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3363,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":291099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1095,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":292195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the in verse of  3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6662,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":298858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1574,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":300434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5215,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":305650,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":957,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":306610,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":312883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6027,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":318912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":39178,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":358092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><b r /> How ever, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":61977,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":420072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":11915,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":431989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1521,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":433513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10 -0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":438497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":47662,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":486161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<s ub>6</su b>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":56644,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":542807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":5007,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":547817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7361,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":555180,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3613,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":558796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questi ons as a ccurately as possible.","rt":26106,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":584904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":587883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1465,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":589351,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2818,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":592171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4156,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":596329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6644,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":602975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3733,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":606722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":612801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 - 4 plus 1 equals five therefor it's under 9 so the number stays the same as when it was added.","response_history":["5- 4 plus 1 equals five therefor it's under 9 so the sumber stays the same as when it was added.","5 - 4 plus 1 equals five therefor it's under 9 so the sumber stays the same as when it was added.","5 - 4 plus 1 equals five therefor it's under 9 so the umber stays the same as when it was added.","5 - 4 plus 1 equals five therefor it's under 9 so the number stays the same as when it was added."],"rt":53295,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":666098,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 8 plus 4 equals 12 do it is higher than 9 and we must subtract 9 from 12 to get the correct answer","response_history":["3 8 plus 4 equals 12 do it is higher than 9 and we must subtract 9 from 12 to get the correct answer"],"rt":40569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":706669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 would be the identity since 9 minus it's self would be 0. as an example if we had 7+2 the answer would be 0","response_history":["0 would be the identity since 9 minus it's self would be 0. as an example if we had 7+2 the answer would be 0"],"rt":86171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":792842,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub> 9</sub>? ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"I honestly can't not remember the rules of this operation. I think it may be 4 since 5+4 would equal 9 and then - 9 would be 0.","response_history":["I think I","I honestly can't not remember the rules of this opertation.","I honestly can't not remember the rules of this operation. I think it may be 4 since 5+4 would equal 9 and then - 9 would be 0."],"rt":161247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":954093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"I think the answer is 7 I cannot remember this rule.","response_history":["I think the answer is 7 I cannot remember this rule."],"rt":36868,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":990965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the  inverse  of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"I think it would be 9 because it would equal 0","response_history":["I think it would be 9 because it would equal 0"],"rt":25960,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1016927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Hmm now I may remember- Is 3+3+3 equals nine then the result would be 0 so the answer should be 3?","response_history":["I think the answer is","Hmm now I may rememebe","Hmm now I may rememeber- Is 3+3+3 equals nine then the result would be 0 so the answer should be 3?","Hmm now I may remember- Is 3+3+3 equals nine then the result would be 0 so the answer should be 3?"],"rt":126708,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1143637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't think so because 2 cannot produce 1,3 or 5","response_history":["I don't think so because 2 cannot produce 1,3 or 5"],"rt":50384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1194024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3+3+3+3+3 that would equal 15 and minus 9 that would be 4.","response_history":["yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the 5th power i","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the  5th pow er ","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the 5th powe","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the 5th pow","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the 5th","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the 5t","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the 5","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the ","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to the","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to th","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 to t","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 t","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3 ","yes.. I think because it can make the other numbers.. like if you did 3+3+3+3+3  that wo uld equal 15 and minus 9 that would be 4."],"rt":122875,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1316901,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"hmm now I'm confused. No I don't think it can be because 5 even added together multiple times can-t make 2 if you subtract 9.","response_history":["yes because 5 can make the other numbers if added together and th","hmm now I'm confused. No I don't think it can be because 5-9 c","hmm now I'm confused. No I don't think it can be because 5-9 ","hmm now I'm confused. No I don't think it can be because 5-9","hmm now I'm confused. No I don't think it can be because 5-","hmm now I'm confused. No I don't think it can be because 5 even added together multiple times can-t make 2 if you subtract 9."],"rt":96769,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1413673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because eventually after adding the number 6 with other numbers and then subtracting 9 from those totals can get all the lower numbers. like 6+4 would be 1 6+5 would be 2 and so on.","response_history":["yes because eventually after adding numb","yes because eventually after adding num","yes because eventually after adding nu","yes because eventually after adding n","yes because eventually after adding the number 6 a","yes because eventually after adding the number 6 over and over","yes because eventually after adding the number 6 with other numbers and then subtracting 9 from those totals can get all the lower numbers. like 6+4 would be 1 6+5 would be 2 and so on."],"rt":101767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1515443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":37526,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1552973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+1n","response_history":["+1n"],"rt":24426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1577400,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words ho w you go t your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I think it would be +xn because wouldn't the cancel them out? I'm really not sure... since there is no number it's just the letter x","response_history":["I think it would be x","I think it would be +xN","I think it would be +xn because wouldn't the cancle them out? I'm really not sure","I think it would be +xn because wouldn't the cancel them out? I'm really not sure... since nverse woul","I think it would be +xn because wouldn't the cancel them out? I'm really not sure... since there is no number it's just the letter x"],"rt":144271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1721676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I thought I saw a pattern but now I'm not sure-- I thought and odd plus and odd or and even plus an odd would make all the lower numbers but with not seeing anything else I have no idea if x can be a generator","response_history":["I thought I saw a pattern but now I'm not sure-- I thought and odd plus and odd or and even plus an odd would make all the lower numbers but with not seeing anything else I have no idea if x ca ","I thought I saw a pattern but now I'm not sure-- I thought and odd plus and odd or and even plus an odd would make all the lower numbers but with not seeing anything else I have no idea if x can be a generator"],"rt":99778,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1821456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"Tr ue","response_history":["True"],"rt":12524,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1833984,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":16487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1850474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":20756,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1871231,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a genera tor unde r +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"false like if 3 was x and 9 was n- 3 can go into 9 3 times but with other numbers can be combined to make it to where 3 would make all the smaller numbers.","response_history":["Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divded into it- a","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divded into it- ","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- Wait no it's false because say that 3 is x a nis 9","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- Wait no it's false because say that 3 is x a nis ","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I thin k it wou ld have be able to be divided into it- Wait no it's false because say that 3 is x a nis","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- Wait no it's false because say that 3 is x a ni","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- Wait no it's false because say that 3 is x a n is 9-","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- Wait no it's false because say that 3 is x a n is 9.","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- Wai","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- Wa","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- W","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then  I think  it would have be able to be divided into it- ","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it-","Well if x cannot make all the other numbers bellow n then I think it would have be able to be divided into it- like if 3 was x and 9 was n- 3 can go into 9 3 times but it cannot","f like if 3 was x and 9 was n- 3 can go into 9 3 times but it cannot","fal like if 3 was x and 9 was n- 3 can go into 9 3 times but it cannot","fals like if 3 was x and 9 was n- 3 can go into 9 3 times but it cannot","false like if 3 was x and 9 was n- 3 can go into 9 3 times but it cannot","false like if 3 was x and 9 was n- 3 can go into 9 3 times but with other numbers can be combined to make it to where 3 would make all the smaller numbers."],"rt":274135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2145369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, i s its in verse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":32223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2177599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"No because then 9 could not be subtracted to make 0","response_history":["yes because even when the numbers are added togther th ","yes because even when the numbers are added togther the principle is still the same like x is just x twice","No because then 9 could not be subtracted to make 0"],"rt":162041,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2339644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":13352,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2352998,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2916,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2355916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"40","response_history":["40"],"rt":3511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2359429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":5014,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2364445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"math 092 and I couldn't even complete it because I could not understand algebra what so ever.","response_history":["math 092 and I couldn't even complete it because math problems","math 092 and  I couldn 't even complete it because math","math 092 and I couldn't even complete it because mat","math 092 and I couldn't even complete it because ma","math 092 and I couldn't even complete it because m","math 092 and I couldn't even complete it because I could not understan algebra what so ever.","math 092 and I couldn't even complete it because I could not understand algebra what so ever."],"rt":51501,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2415949,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":7516,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2423467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":7288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2430757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5293,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2436052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":8224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2444278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3037,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2447317,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2450204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6011,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2456216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no and i wish i would have to write down what thee rules of each thing were.. I had forgot what was what by the time I had to use them.","response_history":["no and i wih","no and i wish i would have to write down what thee rules of each thing were.. I had forgot what was what by the time I had to use them."],"rt":44659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2500877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 5-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It was hard and at first I thought I had the hand of it but with out being able to look back and refresh my memory on what exactly the rules for inverse and the like were made it quite frustrating.","response_history":["It was hard and at first I thought I had the hand of it but with out being able to look back at ","It was hard and at first I thought I had the hand of it but with out being able to look back at","It was hard and at first I thought I had the hand of it but with out being able to look back a","It was hard and at first I thought I had the hand of it but with out being able to look back and refresh my memory on what exactly the rules for inverse and the like were made it quite frustrating."],"rt":57111,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2557990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]